adenandanais.com 2015-09-08

# privacy policy | aden + anais USA

aden + anais respects your privacy and takes reasonable measures to protect your personal information. This privacy statement is intended to make you aware of the information we collect from you and how we use that information. Changes to this statement and our practices will be provided [here](http://www.adenandanais.com/en-us/content/info+privacy/privacy-policy.aspx). We encourage you to check here periodically to make sure you are aware our most current practices. 

This website is intended for individuals at the age of 18 and over. If you are under 18 years old, please do not use this website. Instead, ask your parent or guardian to shop here for you. 

This website is intended for use in the United States of America and the Federal and State laws of the United States apply. By using and shopping on this website you acknowledge and agree that the personal data protection laws of other jurisdictions do not apply. If you are a citizen of another country you agree to the use of your personal data as outlined in this statement. Please note that aden + anais has global websites for [different territories](http://www.adenandanais.com/en-us/content/global+web-shops/our-global-web-shops.aspx). If you are located outside of the United States, we encourage you to shop at one of our global stores. 

## What We Collect

Directly From You

aden + anais collects information that you actively give us via this website, telephone, email and when you sign up for our newsletter. 

When you place an order via [www.adenandanais.com](http://www.adenandanais.com/), the information you give us includes your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, email and the merchandise you order. aden + anais does not receive or obtain your credit card information. When you enter your credit card details, you are directed to our credit card processing company; Charge Logic. Charge Logic collects and processes your credit card payment on behalf of aden + anais. You can visit their website for details on [Chare Logic’s security measures](https://www.chargelogic.com/security). 

If you sign up for our newsletter, you will provide us your email address and possibly the city and state where you are located. 

Indirectly From You

aden + anais uses cookies for website functionality and analytics information. We may collect other information about customers of aden + anais products from merchants who carry our products. 

Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed and stored on your browser when you visit a website. Cookies help to keep your settings, log in information and other customizations when you return to certain websites. They also help with overall website functionality. aden + anais uses cookies to help this website functional well, for customer service purposes and to learn about visitors to this website. Cookies will let aden + anais know what website you came from, what sections of this website you visit when you are here and other analytical information. 

During certain marketing campaigns, aden + anais may work with third parties to place anonymous cookies on your browser. This type of cookie works in conjunction with pixels, small pieces of code on our website. The pixel related cookies communicate with specified websites when a visitor using the same browser goes to the other website. In this type of marketing campaign aden + anais visitors may see advertisements or reminders about our products and services after leaving our website. 

aden + anais uses Google Analytics for reports on visitor website use. The Google Analytics service uses cookies to track adenandanias.com usage. Goolge Analytics shares this information with other Google services, including its advertising network. For more information, please read the Google Analytics use of cookies [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). 

You can change your browser settings at any time so that it will not automatically accept cookies or to clear cookies from your browser. 

Do Not Track

You have the ability to enable your browser settings to “Do Not Track.” Doing this sends a signal to websites, ad networks and plug-in providers about your browsing preferences. adenand anais.com does not respond to the Do Not Track browser signal. 

## Sharing Information

aden + anais does not sell, rent or trade the information you provide us with third parties. We do share only the information necessary to fulfill your orders with those third parties who support our processing and shipping of merchandise. We may also share the information you provide us with third parties with whom we have agreements to provide promotional offers for our products, news and information, specific marketing campaigns and, in order to keep our customer service database up to date. We do not authorize these third parties to make any other use of your information. 

If we are required by law to provide information to law enforcement or other authorities, we will make available the information that is demanded of us. 

aden + anais reserves the right to use and/or share aggregated, not directly identifiable information about our customers and website visitors with third parties. This information includes the number and types of purchasers and visitors to this website. In making this information available, aden + anais does not directly reveal your personal identity. 

## How We Use Your Information

First and foremost aden + anais uses the information you provide us to fulfill your orders and respond to your inquiries. We may also use your information to send you special promotions and information about other products you may enjoy, to remind you of uncompleted orders and to send you our newsletter if you choose to receive it. You have the ability to easily request that you stop receiving promotions, offers and our newsletter. 

## Social Media Other Website Links

You may find social media plug-ins or buttons on the aden + anais website. These enable you to directly access the aden + anais pages on social media platforms such as Twitter, Facebook and Pinterest. Similarly, you may find links on this website to other websites. aden + anais is not connected to these third parties and has no control over them, we simply make the links available for your convenience. Please be aware that when you click on one of the plug-ins or url links you are leaving the aden + anais website and going to those third party platforms and websites. When you do so, you will be subject to the terms, conditions and policies of those third parties. We encourage you to read those in order to understand what information you may be sharing with those platforms and websites. 

Please send any concerns regarding our privacy practices or this statement to: [customerservice@adenandanais.com](mailto:customerservice@adenandanais.com) or to:  
aden + anais, Inc  
20 Jay St, Suite 600  
Brooklyn, NY 11201

Updated June 2015
